http://andrearose.com/terms_privacy.asp

Gift Certificates
For Customer Service or Phone Orders Please Call Us:     310-470-0691
Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to
www.andrearose.com
and ANDREA ROSE INC and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to ANDREA ROSE INC include
www.andrearose.com
The ANDREA ROSE INC website is a Personal Care Products-Cosmetics site. By using the ANDREA ROSE INC website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Use of your Personal Information
ANDREA ROSE INC collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
ANDREA ROSE INC may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from ANDREA ROSE INC and its affiliates.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
ANDREA ROSE INC does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
ANDREA ROSE INC may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to ANDREA ROSE INC, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
ANDREA ROSE INC may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on ANDREA ROSE INC or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of ANDREA ROSE INC; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of ANDREA ROSE INC, or the public.
Automatically Collected Information
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by ANDREA ROSE INC. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the ANDREA ROSE INC website.
Use of Cookies
The ANDREA ROSE INC website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize ANDREA ROSE INC pages, or register with ANDREA ROSE INC site or services, a cookie helps ANDREA ROSE INC to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same ANDREA ROSE INC website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the ANDREA ROSE INC features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the ANDREA ROSE INC services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information ANDREA ROSE INC secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. ANDREA ROSE INC uses the following methods for this purpose:
- SSL Protocol
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.
Children Under Thirteen
ANDREA ROSE INC does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
E-mail Communications
From time to time, ANDREA ROSE INC may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication.
If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from ANDREA ROSE INC, you may opt out of such communications by Clicking on the unsubscribe button.
External Data Storage Sites
We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.
Changes to this Statement
ANDREA ROSE INC reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.
Contact Information
ANDREA ROSE INC welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that ANDREA ROSE INC has not adhered to this Statement, please contact ANDREA ROSE INC at:
ANDREA ROSE INC PO BOX 11503 BEVERLY HILLS, CA 90213
Email Address: theroseinc@hotmail.com
Telephone number: 1-888-712-ROSE Effective as of May 29, 2018
Copyright © 2013 Andrea Rose Inc. DBA Personal Basics by Andrea Rose. All Rights Reserved.
